Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5728
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Office Files, 1973
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1961 Wage and Rules Movement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Radio-Telephone Equipment Communications, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1962 Rules Movement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway - Section 6 Notice, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Florida East Coast Railway, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Includes order from District Court judge in re disbursement of funds awarded in damages to non-operating employees and others as a result of the strike.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Louisville and Nashville "No Injury" Reports, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Wage and Rules Movement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Changes in Discipline Policy and Procedure, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Employment and Medical Examination Policy and Procedures, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Norfolk and Western's Railway Thrift Plan for Non-Union Employees, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Compulsory Retirement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1966 Wages-Rules Movement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1967 Wage-Rules Movement - Guaranteed Annual Wage, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Penn Central - Thrift Plan, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1969 Wage-Rules Movement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1970 Wage-Rules Movement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Circulars from the Railway Employes' Department, AFL- CIO.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: 1973 Wage Rules Movement - Railway Employees Department, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Circulars from the Railway Employes' Department, AFL-CIO and the BMoW. Also contains 1973 National Shop Crafts Agreement.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Guaranteed Annual Wage, Etcetera - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    BRAC national rules and wage movement.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Health and Welfare, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Travelers' Insurance Group Policy GA-23000. Also includes informational pamphlets on Social Security benefits.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Insurance Company [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 50a)
    Group insurance policies.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Insurance Company [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 5, Folder 50b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Operating Unions, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Rules Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Carrier Strike Insurance Program, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Automation, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Shop (General), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Union Dues (General), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Diversification of Railroads - "Piggybacking", 1973 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Permits on Railroad Property for Union Business, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Railway Labor Building, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    Financial reports.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committees (General), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Safety Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Meet with AAR - Railroad Labor-Management Relations, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    Includes correspondence and minutes of committee meetings in re addressing employee substance abuse, applications of and amendments to the Civil Rights Act of 1964, the situation on the Northeast Corridor with regard to Penn Central's financial woes, and the fuel crisis.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    Includes minutes of committee meetings.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, Etcetera, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    Includes information on the inclusion of the Milwaukee Road in the Burlington Northern merger.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: American Association of Railroads-Railway Labor Executives Association Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Political Education Committee (PEC), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    Includes correspondence in re effects of carrier bankruptcies in Northeast on pensions.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: In-Plant Education Program for Cooperating Railroad Brotherhoods (Chicago Area), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on Railway Labor Act, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Legislative Representatives, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Committee on "C.O.A.L." (Council of Allied Labor) Burlington Northern, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Passes, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Personnel Records (General), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Prospective Employees (General), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    RESTRICTED
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Workmen's Compensation Tax, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial (General), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Travelers Insurance (Employee Forms), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Financial Statements, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    Monthly financial reports on RLEA's assets.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: G.P.O. Account Number 11256, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Insurance (General), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Postage Meter, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Addressograph - Multigraph Corporation, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: The Xerox Copying Machine, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Office Furniture (General), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers (General), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers' Bills January - June [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4a)
    Bills invoiced by legal matter.
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers' Bills January - June [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers' Bills July-December[folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5a)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Lawyers' Bills July-December [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5b)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Strikes (General), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Florida East Coast Railway Strike, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Shop Crafts Dispute, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Railway Labor Executives Association: Signalmen's Strike 1971, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: General, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Report from The Chessie System on cost of rehabilitation of facilities in Port Austin, Michigan.
  - Railroads: Railroad Ownership, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    New organization structure of the Western and Maryland.
  - Railroads: Penn Central, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Railroads: Auto Train Corporation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads - Highway User Charges, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Railroads: Astro, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Railroads: Western Railroad Association, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Railroads: Carriers' Conference Committees (General), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Circulars in re arbitration awards.
  - Railroads: National Railway Labor Conference, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations (General), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Railroads: Kansas City Southern, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Railroads: Missouri Pacific, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Railroads: Southern Pacific Hospital Department, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Railroads: Western Pacific Hospital Association, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations - MEDICARE, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Railroads: Tuition Aid Program - Union Pacific Railroad, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Railroads: Air Freight, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Railroads: Western and Atlantic Railroad - Proposed Lease by Southern, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 30a)
    Bulletins. Also includes pamphlet "Why Richard Nixon must be impeached now."
  - Other Organizations: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 30b)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Civil Rights Department, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Free Trade Union News, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Minutes, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - Legislative Action Bulletin, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Legislative Council, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Executive Council, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Bulletins and statement papers.
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Advertising Council, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Includes promotional pamphlets on safety initiatives.
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Other Organizations: Harvard University Trade Union Program, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Other Organizations: The Unions Retirement Foundation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Other Organizations: United States Committee for the United Nations (Also General United Nations), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Other Organizations: National Conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Other Organizations: Research Institute of America - Recommendations, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Other Organizations: Transportation Research Forum, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Other Organizations: American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a Sound Monetary Policy, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Other Organizations: The Labor/Management Committee for Fair Foreign Competition, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Other Organizations: Charities (General), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Other Organizations: American Red Cross, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Other Organizations: Dual Organizations "Paper and Rump", 1973 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau of Middle West, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Other Organizations: LABOR Newspaper, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    Includes financial reports and By-Laws.
  - Other Organizations: Special Election Year Editions of Labor, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Other Organizations: City of Hope, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Other Organizations: Annual Conference of Mayors, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Other Organizations: National Transportation Week, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Railroad Passengers (NARP), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Other Organizations: Conference of Transportation Trades, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - International Affairs: General, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - International Affairs: Bureau of International Labor Affairs (Foreign Visitors), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - International Affairs: Team Managers - Office of International Labor Affairs, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - International Affairs: Trade Union Advisory Committee Department of Labor, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - International Affairs: Joint United States-Mexican Trade Union Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - International Affairs: International Labor Office (ILO), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - International Affairs: News from the International Labor Office, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - International Affairs: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - International Affairs: Press Release, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - International Affairs: News Release, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - International Affairs: Radio Service, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - International Affairs: SPOTLIGHT, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - International Affairs: Press Communique, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - International Affairs: Information Bulletin, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers Federation (ITF), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Commuter Problems: General, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Commuter Problems: Passenger Service Investigation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Commuter Problems: Philadelphia Service Improvement Corporation, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven - Including New York Area, Long Island - Staten Island, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Commuter Problems: New England Railroad Study, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Commuter Problems: Bay Area Rapid Transit, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    Urban Mass Transit Act Grant Application and supporting materials.
  - Commuter Problems: Port Authority Transit Hudson (PATH) [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 87a)
    Urban Mass Transit Act Grant Application for Plainfield Corridor Service Corridor and supporting materials. Contains photographs, maps, pamphlets, and promotional materials.
  - Commuter Problems: Port Authority Transit Hudson (PATH) [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 6, Folder 87b)
  - Commuter Problems: Adequacies - General, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Commuter Problems: Adequacies - Passenger Service of Southern Pacific between California and Louisiana, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Commuter Problems: Adequacies - Passenger Service between San Francisco and Chicago Docket Number 34294, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Urban Mass Transportation Administration Cases [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 91a)
    Approved June 1972-June 1973. Bound volumes listing successful projects.
  - Urban Mass Transportation Administration Cases [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 91b)
  - Commuter Problems: Interstate Commerce Commission Investigation, Suspense Docket 8436 - Penn Central Elimination - Baggage Checking, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Commuter Problems: Commuter Service Improvements - Housing and Urban Development Mass Transit Grants, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Correspondence in re various projects financed by grants.
  - Commuter Problems: Urban Mass Transportation Administration Application IL-03-0031 - Illinois Department of Transportation Commuter Parking Facility, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3a)
  - Commuter Problems: Urban Mass Transportation Administration Applications, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3b)
    Includes application of New Jersey to improve Erie-Lackawanna facilities and to purchase passenger cars
  - Commuter Problems: Section 13(c) Agreement - Massachusetts Bay Transport Authority, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Commuter Problems: Section 13(c) Agreement - Chicago - Loop and West Suburban, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commuter Problems: Southern Pennsylvania Transportation Project Hatboro-Warminster, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Commuter Problems: Lake Porter County - Crown Point, Indiana (Urban Mass Transportation Administration), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Commuter Problems: Washington Metro Area Transit Authority, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Commuter Problems: Revised Final Application of the Delaware River Port Authority for a Mass Transportation Capital Improvement Grant, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    CRU File. October 20, 1972. Bound. Includes photographs, schematics, maps, and other supporting materials.
- Series II: Desk Files, 1973
  - Desk File: January-March [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10a)
    Outgoing correspondence files of the executives of RLEA
  - Desk File: January-March [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10b)
  - Desk File: April-June [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11a)
  - Desk File: April-June [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11b)
  - Desk File: July-September, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Desk File: October-December, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Series III: Office Files, 1974
  - Government: Constitution, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Government: Executive Branch, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Includes list of materials turned over to the Judiciary Committee by Richard Nixon and a timeline of events after the Watergate break-in.
  - Government: Executive Branch, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    CRU File. No records contained in folder when collection accessioned.
  - Government: Environmental Protection Agency, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Government: Accident Investigations, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration (FRA) News, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration: Rail Labor Luncheon Meetings, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Government: Railroad Electrification, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    CRU File.
  - Government: Executive Branch: Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    CRU File. EPA regulations on railroad noise.
  - Government: House and Senate, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Government: House and Senate, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Government: Congressional Campaign Contribution Requests, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Government: Congressional Campaign Contribution Requests, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Government: Appointment of Federal Judgeships, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Government: Appointment of Federal Judgeships, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Government: Government Agencies (General), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Includes EPA guideline on noise levels for railroads, pamphlets on economic indicators,
  - Government Agencies - General, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Government: State Department (General), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Correspondence in re guest worker programs and immigration law.
  - Government: Defense Department, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Government: Department of Transportation, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    CRU File. Bulletins
  - Government: Defense Department (General), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Government: Department of Transportation - Staff Appointments, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Government: Transportation Association of America - E.H. Harriman Awards (Department of Transportation), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    CRU File. Includes reports on safety statistics for carriers.
  - Government: Department of Transportation Federal Highway Administration, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    CRU File. Includes memoranda and correspondence in re railroad safety standards. Also includes NRSB's 1971 annual report to Congress and pamphlets published by the NTSB on its organizational structure.
  - Government: National Transportation Safety Board: Accident Investigations, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration: News, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    CRU File. Includes pamphlet "Guidelines for Writing Railroad Operating Rules" and a bibliography of the published research papers of the FRA in 1973.
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration: Department of Transportation - Congress of Railway Unions (CRU) Recommendations for Staff Appointments, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    CRU File. RESTRICTED
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration Staff Appointments, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Government: 12-Member Operating Rules Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration Safety Hearings, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Government: Qualification Standards - Safety Inspection Positions, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Congress of Railway Unions: File Guide, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    List of CRU Files with material in them that the RLEA does not carry.
  - Federal Railroad Administration, Office of Railroad Safety - Railroad-Highway Safety, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    CRU File. Includes proceedings of 1972 conference on railway safety
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminars (General), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    CRU File. Includes announcement of seminars and locations where they will be offered.
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (Columbus, Ohio. November 20, 1974) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Railway Labor: Federal Safety Seminar (Boston, Massachusetts. October 24, 1974) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar - List for 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (Midland Hotel, Chicago, Illinois. August 7, 1974) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (Portland, Oregon. September 25, 1974) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Railway Labor: Safety Law Seminars - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (Denver, Colorado. June 26, 1974) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (New Orleans, Louisiana. March 27, 1974.) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Railroad Labor: Safety Seminar (St Louis, Missouri. May 22, 1974.) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Railway Labor: Safety Forms (Blank), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (Sacramento, California. April 25, 1974) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (Los Angeles, California. April 23, 1974) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Railroad Labor: Federal Safety Law Seminar (Houston, Texas. January 30, 1974.) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Railroad Labor: Safety Law Seminar - Reservation Forms (Hapeville, Georgia. November 15, 1973/) (Box 8, Folder 16)
    CRU File. Includes educational materials from the DOT.
  - Railroad Labor: Safety Law Seminar - Reservation Forms (Houston, Texas. January 30, 1974.) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Government: Federal Railroad Administration: 12-Member Operating Rules Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)